<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE cXML SYSTEM "http://xml.cxml.org/schemas/cXML/1.2.044/cXML.dtd">
<cXML payloadID="1591960300433.551515782.000082460@qKSFQFj+LepIG++gh3e7PQEQc5M=" timestamp="2020-06-12T04:11:40-07:00" version="1.2.044" >
    <Header>
        <From>
            <Credential domain="DUNS">
                <Identity>AN02005757092-T</Identity>
            </Credential>
        </From>
        <To>
            <Credential domain="DUNS">
                <Identity>AN02005757093-T</Identity>
            </Credential>
        </To>
        <Sender>
            <Credential domain="NetworkID">
                <Identity>AN01000000001</Identity>
            </Credential>
            <UserAgent>Buyer 14s2</UserAgent>
        </Sender>
    </Header>
    <Request deploymentMode="production">
        <StatusUpdateRequest>
            <DocumentReference payloadID="AF78FNK8t8yvvZr13GQT-1ZqUhGX_CIGSDRID_AN02003013689-T"/>
            <Status code="200" text=""/>
            <InvoiceStatus type="rejected">
                <InvoiceIDInfo invoiceDate="2020-06-30T00:00:00-08:00" invoiceID="RIT_PIDX_INVR_DUNS"/>
                <PartialAmount>
                    <Money alternateAmount="" alternateCurrency="" currency="USD">0.00</Money>
                </PartialAmount>
                <Comments xml:lang="en">Comment: [MDC] Devon is disputing this invoice for the following reason(s). We are
                    not able to process this invoice, because credit memo lines must be submitted via the original invoice or
                    entered as a discount to the line item. If the credit is for a discount to the current invoice you will
                    enter a discount to the line item not to exceed or equal the amount of the line item. Discounts may be
                    split between more than one line if necessary. If the credit line is due to a change in a previous
                    invoice entry please submit a credit memo by locating the original invoice in your Ariba outbox or email,
                    then selecting the credit memo button to enter the information. If you have any questions or concerns,
                    please contact DevonDirect@dvn.com. OR view the video tutorials at
                    http://www.devonenergy.com/operations/supply-chain/information. (Zelene Estrada,
                    2020-06-12T04:03:23-07:00) Header Level Exceptions: Contract Review This invoice reconciliation has been
                    determined to have a contract or BPO and needs to be reviewed. Line item: Line Number:1 Part
                    Number:1095537 Description:1095537-AL ESP WELL TEST RENTAL RATE, MONTHLY Exceptions: Contract Item Date
                    Variance The invoice item's date, Sun, 31 May, 2020, was not in the valid range. Please use a valid
                    contract for invoicing or contact the customer directly if you believe this to be in error. Line item:
                    Line Number:2 Part Number:1100359 Description:1100359-AL MON MONITOR/SURV RNTL-INSPATIAL VRZN Exceptions:
                    Contract Item Date Variance The invoice item's date, Sun, 31 May, 2020, was not in the valid range.
                    Please use a valid contract for invoicing or contact the customer directly if you believe this to be in
                    error. Line item: Line Number:3 Part Number:1095537 Description:1095537-AL ESP WELL TEST RENTAL RATE,
                    MONTHLY Exceptions: Contract Item Date Variance The invoice item's date, Sun, 31 May, 2020, was not
                    in the valid range. Please use a valid contract for invoicing or contact the customer directly if you
                    believe this to be in error. Line item: Line Number:4 Part Number:1100359 Description:1100359-AL MON
                    MONITOR/SURV RNTL-INSPATIAL VRZN Exceptions: Contract Item Date Variance The invoice item's date,
                    Sun, 31 May, 2020, was not in the valid range. Please use a valid contract for invoicing or contact the
                    customer directly if you believe this to be in error. Line item: Line Number:5 Part Number:1095537
                    Description:1095537-AL ESP WELL TEST RENTAL RATE, MONTHLY Exceptions: Contract Item Date Variance The
                    invoice item's date, Sun, 31 May, 2020, was not in the valid range. Please use a valid contract for
                    invoicing or contact the customer directly if you believe this to be in error. Line item: Line Number:6
                    Part Number:1095537 Description:1095537-AL ESP WELL TEST RENTAL RATE, MONTHLY Exceptions: Contract Item
                    Date Variance The invoice item's date, Sun, 31 May, 2020, was not in the valid range. Please use a
                    valid contract for invoicing or contact the customer directly if you believe this to be in error. Line
                    item: Line Number:7 Part Number:1095537 Description:1095537-AL ESP WELL TEST RENTAL RATE, MONTHLY
                    Exceptions: Contract Item Date Variance The invoice item's date, Sun, 31 May, 2020, was not in the
                    valid range. Please use a valid contract for invoicing or contact the customer directly if you believe
                    this to be in error. Line item: Line Number:8 Part Number:1095537 Description:1095537-AL ESP WELL TEST
                    RENTAL RATE, MONTHLY Exceptions: Contract Item Date Variance The invoice item's date, Sun, 31 May,
                    2020, was not in the valid range. Please use a valid contract for invoicing or contact the customer
                    directly if you believe this to be in error. Line item: Line Number:9 Part Number:1101393
                    Description:1101393-AL CONCESSION CREDIT - SERVICES Exceptions: Contract Item Date Variance The invoice
                    item's date, Sun, 31 May, 2020, was not in the valid range. Please use a valid contract for
                    invoicing or contact the customer directly if you believe this to be in error. Line item: Line Number:10
                    Part Number:1095537 Description:1095537-AL ESP WELL TEST RENTAL RATE, MONTHLY Exceptions: Contract Item
                    Date Variance The invoice item's date, Sun, 31 May, 2020, was not in the valid range. Please use a
                    valid contract for invoicing or contact the customer directly if you believe this to be in error.</Comments>
            </InvoiceStatus>
            <Extrinsic name="RejectionReasons"/>
        </StatusUpdateRequest>
    </Request>
</cXML>